大家好
我是小武
今天和大家一同观赏的是
2016年中国大师赛男单决赛
由中国选手林丹
对阵队友陈龙
第一局二比二
龙控正手单过度
龙过度
后场龙抓过度
抢放单推挑正手龙过度
单反控转身回放
龙连续控正手
单劈吊斜线龙反控转身龙过度
后场单下压推挑正手龙过度单停顿
逼起球
正手突击斜线得分
六比四
龙控正手单抽压龙挡远网单反控转身
双方网前较量单快推正手龙过度
单反控转身单推挑正手龙过度
后场抓过度下压
龙推头顶抓过度
头顶杀斜线得分
Five six
加油加油
七比五龙推挑正手单过渡
龙网前跟进单推挑正手龙过度
单网前分斜线龙回放
双方斗网
单快推拉开龙过度
单网前分斜线抓推拦截推头顶龙杀
上网连贯得分
Jin pressure after the roundhead smash there from lyndance
But he kept his cool
Very well
The world number one
七平单网前分斜线龙推挑
正手抓过度进攻单
鱼跃绣球龙上网跟进单快推
正手龙过度单回放
正手突击斜线龙防反
推挑正手单过度龙回放单
推挑过顶龙过度单回放龙连续控两底线
抓过度抢搓单推挑出界
Gives out good leave from chen long he
As anticipated multiple tight points from both
so11比九单发
后场往前推扑空
转身往前分斜线龙回放下压抢搓单推
挑过顶龙过度
后场单下压上网推转身抓过度
往前扑压得分
Off the back end
Look at this closed the court down
So well
Well
Almost getting channong in the circumstances
12比九龙推头顶单下压推
头顶龙过渡
后场单过渡
龙推头顶单滑板
斜线龙回放单推头顶龙下压控网
劈杀斜线单挡网摆脱
龙推头顶单过度
后场隆平高压头顶抓摆脱下压龙推
挑正手抓过度进攻
空转身往前分斜线单反控转身抓过度进攻
单推挑正手抓过度抢搓龙推
挑过顶单斜线过度
龙推头顶抓摆脱
劈掉斜线单挡网摆脱
可惜头顶掉斜线失误哦
What a point point of the match
So far
And you can imagine the perpose
He we need a fire
Extinguishes to put out the fire on their quads
After this long lung busting point
living13比十单抓推
推头顶龙下压空转身抓过度
侧身突击得分
No it's wonderful
He's had fruit from that smash down the line
Tommy court says
Lyndan wonderful power smash here from chen long
Look at this gets behind it
While with that back leg
12比13单放网龙
推头顶单下压推
挑过顶单回放龙推挑过顶单过度龙回放
侧身突击一拍
上网抢推单
高质量蓝调得分
Good control here
Stays in the point
Well
But this one look at that
14比12单发后场龙过渡
后场单过度龙回放
单推挑头顶龙软压龙推挑过顶
抓过度
往前推扑
单反控转身抓过度
往前拦吊得分
Well
Even off the net corhe
Manages to be deceptive flip flicks
It back to the backhand side of chen long
Right here look at this look wow
I just to get chen long slightly off balance
15比12龙控转身龙回放
单推挑正手龙过度
后场单劈吊斜线轮回勾单网
前分斜线杀
上网连贯得分
No there's a synergy to what he's doing right now two plus
Two equal in seventeen lindan
Producing some brilliant
Badminton towards the sharp end of this
Opening game
17比12龙推挑正手抓过度进攻
Massive
龙推挑过顶单斜线过度
龙回放单推头顶龙软压单回勾
龙推头顶抓过度杀
上网连贯得分好
The tenth chapter of their book
These two
The tenth meeting
13比17单推头顶龙下压单扑压头顶
拦截龙挡
原网单推头顶龙过渡
后场单滑板斜线龙反推正手抓过度进攻
龙推挑过顶单推头顶龙下压上网
高质量抢搓得分
It's a great tight net shot
There
Look at this wonderful soft hand skills
16比18单推正手抓过度
侧身突击得分
Yes
Smash down the line from lind
This is how high
Gets up off the floor with the jump
Smash
Laden with power and risnap
19比16
龙接发抢扑龙挡远网单推头顶龙
头顶杀斜线得分
Long good response
Desperate to get on the front for early in the rally
17比19龙发后场放网
单推挑正手龙过度单回放头顶突击直线得分
That's thruss good more to the point
He really injected
20比17龙控正手单过度龙推挑头顶抓过度
侧身突击一拍空转身
但抓过度失误
但赢得了首局比赛的胜利
That snatches
The opening game
Twenty one seventeen in twenty seven minutes
Three one seven eight
Well if there's anything in it's not acknowledging
Each other
On the uh change events
第二局
零比零龙控正手单劈掉斜线龙回放
单网前分对角龙回放
正手突击斜线得分
Indeed his sixth title
That's what he's up for sure
Will be attempting to ratch
It right up through to the top gear of his
Brilliant level to stop lind
二比一
龙头顶突击直线得分
Look how allirty was to get around that with his body
三比一单推挑正手龙滑板吊一拍
单回勾龙回搓单推挑过顶龙过渡单挡
原网龙回放单推正手单放远网龙推挑过顶
抓过度下压单放远网头顶突击斜线得分
To be chu chen chen in the fireball was extended to three games
Though twenty one seventeen in the decider
二比三
龙推挑正手单过度
后场抓过度进攻
龙接杀分
斜线单控转身抓过度进攻
龙高质量接杀转进网得分
Well the right smile as chan long
Extends his lead something
He was unable to do in the opening game
It was all in dan
Leading margin late
八比五单推挑正手龙抽对角单挡网
摆脱龙
推正手单过渡
后场龙同样过度
后场单过渡
龙往前分斜线单推头顶单滑板
斜线龙回放单推挑过顶单放原网
正手突击斜线得分
Oh that is superb from linda
It's so frugal and error
Right now
Playing slightly higher
Margin badminton
But look at this brilliance from lindan
七比九龙推头顶单下压
往前跟进
龙连续控正手
抓过度劈杀斜线单
高质量鱼跃救中龙
推头顶单
抓过度下压龙回放单回勾龙
高质量原网转进网得分
That was almost a miraculous turnaround from lindan
Point of the match
So far that one
Watch this
Channel long just breaking with a little luck
There off the top of the net cord lindan in the fast recovery
Anticipating the aggressive
Deep clear
Uh lifter should take look at this down
But not out get up so quick
八比11龙推
头顶单下压
单推挑正手抓过度下压
龙抓推单接杀分
斜线龙回放单推挑过顶抓过度进攻
龙接杀分
对角单回放
龙回搓抓扑得分
Oh it was the wonderful tight that shot that
Got it done for chen
Long right up to the front of the gordon
Exposing him in that regard right
There look at that and an excellent
Follow up from the
九比12龙推头顶龙过度后场
但同样过渡后场龙斜线过渡单回放
龙推正手抓过度
连续扑压单反打空挡得分
Reflexive brilliance with the flat hard drive
13比11龙侧身突击得分
Oh yes
15比11
单控转身单过渡
后场机会不好
龙选择过度单停顿推
正手龙过度单回搓机会不好
但选择过度龙高点抢放单推挑过顶龙
过度单推头顶龙头顶突击直线得分
17比13
单网前分斜线龙回搓单控转身龙过渡
后场单过渡
龙推扑单挡远网龙反控转身单过渡
龙网前分斜线单反控正手抓过度侧身突击
直线单网前高质量低手位勾对角得分
Absolutely sublime from lyndan deceptive to the max
Take a look at this
It's just as well
Got a slow a camera watch the risk click here
Look at that that a ha was gorgeous
Done with
14比17
单发后场单放远网抓推拦截抓摆脱
进攻单回放龙回搓单控转身
龙过度单挡远网龙推头顶单滑板斜线
龙反控转身推头顶机会不好
龙选择过度单抢
放龙控转身单斜线过渡轮回搓单回勾
龙回搓单反打空挡得分
Absolu arguably point of the match so far
15比17龙控正手单抽压单挡
原网龙反控正手单抓推突击得分
Three road for lindhe's ploring it back
Is that reverse slice
16比17
龙推正手单过度
后场单挡
原网龙回搓龙下鸭
双方斗网龙挑球很到位
龙抓过度逼压龙控
正手抓过度劈杀斜线得分
Chen long bites back with this
First point in the last four with a power smash for that was timely
18比16单抢放头顶突击直线得分
Ha ha ha ha it was a wonderful return here was the look out
Tight that one was
And then a beautiful backup
So hard to read
19比18龙推头顶单下压
双方网前较量
单推挑正手龙过度单挡
远网龙控头顶单软压龙网前分斜线
单推正手往前分
斜线龙连续控两底线
龙抓摆脱反推斜线得分
Who stayed calm throughout
19平单连续控正手
隆平高压正手抓过度
往前扑压得分
二零比19单
连续控两底线
双方网前较量
龙推挑头顶机会不好选择过度单推
正手往前勾
对角下压上网推挑正手龙
过度单推挑正手龙进攻失误
Make the bull by chan long this one here
And here
It is
And he just bills wide
20平龙推正
手抓过度下压抓摆脱
扑压单反顶后场抓摆脱下压
推头顶龙下压推转身推头顶单过度
后场往前分斜线龙反控正手
但抓过度
进攻失误
21平
单网前分斜线龙控网抢攻单接杀弹
斜线抓龙的回球
反打中路得分
22比21单抓推空转身
龙反拍下压推头顶抓摆脱进攻
上网推扑
但抓摆脱乌鸦出界
单以大比分二比零战胜队友
成龙获得了2016年中国大师赛冠军
Raucous applause
After a wondrous match
Lpdwith
His six bonnie
China
Mastercycle
He's delighted
He played some immacula bitton
And takes deserve it adulation
Is sixty third korea title to go with the all england
Open crown
Earlier
This year
Look at that in recovery
Awesome
Frankly
That's how he did it
That was the match point
Ln down through then and straight games
Twenty
One
Seventeen
Twenty
Three twenty